12 billion miles and counting...
The Farthest is a documentary film directed by Emer Reynolds.
The captivating tales of the people and events behind one of humanity's
greatest achievements in exploration: NASA's Voyager mission.
Self (archive footage), played by Carl Sagan.
Self, played by John Casani.
Self, played by Lawrence Krauss.
Self, played by Carolyn Porco.
Self, played by Timothy Ferris.
Self, played by Edward Stone.
The Earthsea Cycle, also known as Earthsea, is a series of high
fantasy books written by American author Ursula K.
Beginning with A Wizard of Earthsea (1968), The Tombs of Atuan (1970), and The Farthest Shore (1972), the
series was continued in Tehanu (1990), and Tales from Earthsea and The Other Wind (both 2001).
In 2018, all the novels and short stories were published in a single volume, The Books of
Earthsea: The Complete Illustrated Edition, with artwork by Charles Vess.
The film explores themes of jupiter, nasa, saturn, based on true story, space.